momentis.net 2014-10-23

# Momentis International LLC Online Privacy Policy

Momentis International LLC Online Privacy Policy
Momentis International LLC (“Momentis”) is committed to preserving and safeguarding your
right to privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out the manner in which we will collect, use,
disclose and otherwise manage your personal information.
Collection of Personal Information
We collect personal information that you provide us when you:
        Sign up for one of our products or services;
        Access our Web site;
        Contact our customer service department;
        Provide us with comments or suggestions; or
        Make payments online.
Information we may request includes your email address, name, home address, and telephone
number, credit card and billing information. We may also ask for your Social Security Number or
Social Insurance Number to process your credit or financing request.
We may collect information about your visits to our websites, including the pages you view, the
links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the Momentis websites and
services. We may also collect certain information from the browser you used to come to our
website, such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type and language, access times, the
Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the website that referred you to our website and to which
URL you browse away from our site if you click on a link on our site.
How We Use Personal Information
Momentis uses your personal information to:
        Develop, enhance, market or provide products and services;
        Send communications to you such as information about products and services available
         from Momentis or its affiliates;
        Enforce our contract(s);
        Prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities;
        Meet legal and regulatory requirements; or
        Otherwise, as disclosed to you at the point of collection.
Personal information collected may be stored and processed in Canada, the United States or
any other country in which Momentis or its corporate affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain
facilities, and by using Momentis products or services (including our website), you consent to
any such transfer of information outside of your country.
Information is retained for the duration of any contract period, as well as for a period of up to 10
years after the termination of customer contracts and any renewals thereof.

Other Parties with Whom Momentis May Share Personal Information
We may share your personal information with Momentis affiliates, subsidiaries or agents to
provide you with product(s) or service(s) you request or to make our business of that of our
corporate affiliates more responsive to your needs. We may also disclose your personal
information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, or other legal action; as
required by law or regulation; or if Momentis reasonably believes it is necessary to protect
Momentis or its affiliates, its customers, or the public. In addition, we may share your personal
information with business partners that help Momentis or its affiliates analyze and/or improve
our communication or relationship with you. Momentis or its affiliates may also provide your
personal information to government entities to determine your eligibility for particular product(s)
or service(s). Except as described above, we will not disclose your personal information to third
parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have provided consent.
How You can Access Your Information
Momentis wants to help you keep your personal information accurate. To review, verify or
correct your personal information, please contact our customer service department in writing.
Momentis may not be able to provide you with access to your personal information, where such
refusal is permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements. Momentis will
inform you of the reasons why, subject to any legal or regulatory restrictions, access has been
denied.
Selecting Your Communication Preferences
You may change or withdraw your consent to receive marketing communications from
Momentis any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice, by
contacting Momentis’ customer service department. In some circumstances, a change in or
withdrawal of consent may limit our ability to provide products or services to, or acquire products
or services from, you. Because some marketing communications are developed in advance, you
may sometimes receive solicitations after we receive a change in your consent to provide you
with communications.
We assume, unless you advise us otherwise, that by receiving a copy of this privacy statement
or by continuing to deal with Momentis or its affiliated entities, you have consented to the
collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as explained in this privacy
statement.
Safeguarding Personal Information
Momentis is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety
of technological, physical and organizational protections and procedures to help protect your
personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, such as encryption,
passwords, physical security, etc. While we strive to protect your personal information,
Momentis cannot ensure or warrant that the personal information or private communications you
transmit to us will always remain private, and you do so at your own risk.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your
responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If
you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or
service     to    protect    access      to   your   information    from     subsequent      users.
We will not require you to transmit your SSN on the Internet unless the connection is secure or
the SSN is encrypted, or require you to transmit your SSN to access a website without requiring
additional authentication.
Use of 'Cookies'
When you access Momentis’ website, some information in the form of a "cookie" or similar file
may be automatically downloaded to your computer. This helps us to enhance the on-line
experience of visitors to our sites. If you do not want cookies sent to or stored on your system,
most Internet browsers will allow you to delete cookies from your computer hard drive, prevent
them from being stored or signal a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your
browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Children’s Online Privacy
Momentis’ website is not indented for use by children and does not knowingly collect any
information from children under the age of 14.
Changes to Our Privacy Statement
We will occasionally update this privacy statement. If we make changes to the privacy statement
regarding how Momentis will use your personal information, we will revise the privacy statement
to reflect such changes and revise the statement's effective date, included at the end of this
section. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how
Momentis is protecting your personal information.
Contacting Us
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write to us
at the following address:
Momentis International US LLC
5085 W. Park Blvd, Ste 200
Plano, TX 75093
You may also email us at: repservices@momentis.net
Privacy Statement Effective Date: April 1, 2014
